const quiz = [
    {
        question: "What is the most popular tourist destination in Sri Lanka?",
        options: [
            "Kandy",
            "Galle",
            "Colombo",
            "Dabulla"
        ],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question: "What is the main language spoken in Sri Lanka?",
        options: [
            "Tamil",
            "English",
            "Sinhala",
            "Urdu"
        ],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question: "What is the most famous Archeological Treasure and UNESCO named World Heritage in Sri Lanka?",
        options: [
            "Tempale of the Tooth",
            "Adam's peak",
            "Ancient City of Sigiriya",
            "Galle fort"
        ],
        answer:2
    },
    {
        question:
            "What is the main religion in Sri Lanka?",
        options: [
            "Buddhism",
            "Hinduism",
            "Christianity",
            "Islam"
        ],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:
            "What is the name of famous tea-growing region in Sri Lanka?",
        options: [
            "Galle",
            "Dabulla",
            "jaffna",
            "Nuwara Eliya"
        ],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of famous wildlife park located in Sri Lanka?",
        options: [
            "Wilpattuwa National Park",
            "Minneriya National Park", 
            "Singharaja National Park",
            "Yala National Park"
        ],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question: "Which season is the best for visiting Sri Lanka?",
        options: [
            "Winter (December-February)",
            "Spring (March-May)",
            "Summer (June-August)",
            "Autumn (September-November)"
        ],
        answer:0
    },
    {
        question:
            "Which is the most popular beach destination in Sri Lanka?",
        options: [
            "Mirissa",
            "Tangalle",
            "Negombo",
            "Unawatuna"
        ],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question: "What is the most popular beach activity in Sri Lanka?",
        options: [
            "Jet skiing",
            "Surfing",
            "Snorkeling",
            "Beach volleyball"
        ],
        answer:1
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the traditional Sri Lankan costume worn buy women?",
        options: [
            "Kandyan saree","Salwar Kameez", "Sarong", "Sari"],
        answer:0
    },
]
